# **CARRIER RESUME**

#### PERSONAL DETAIL:

Name : Dani Lesmiadi

Date of Birth : Bandung, February 11<sup>th</sup> 1981

Nationality : Indonesian

Education : Bachelor Degree, University of Computing

(UNIKOM), 2004

Address : Jl. Baturahayu no.71, Buahbatu, Bandung

Email Address : dani.lesmiadi@gmail.com

Phone : +62-8122-44-3582



Over the last five years I have continuously striven to gain and improve my knowledge throughout all aspects of the web design and development. I became fascinated with web design and development when a friend of mind ask me to build a web driven system, to manage daily transportation activity with real-time reports for internal members as well as external vendors and clients at the company where he was working. Through studying at university I have acquired the required skills and understanding that is needed for this role. I have superb algorithmic and programming skills and appreciate excellent design along with usability and interactivity. I enjoyed overcoming problems and working to deadlines for clients. Working as a team excited me as we would often bounce ideas off each other, but I also enjoy working as an individual.

I have such a high desire to succeed in this role that I will do all I can to become successful. I will work flexibly and any hours required of me to finish the task in hand. I am highly motivated and believe in my ability. I always do everything I can to ensure that I keep up to date with changes in the industry so that my work is always current.

#### KNOWLEDGE IN SOFTWARES

- 1. Ms. Project
- 2. Photoshop
- 3. HTML
- 4. CSS
  - Plain CSS
  - SCSS
  - Bootstrap
  - Bulma
  - Materialize CSS
  - Vuetify
- 5. Javascript
  - Native Javascript

- Jquery
- Node JS
- VUE is
- 6. Server Side Language
  - PHP
  - Laravel
  - Code Igniter
- 7. Database MySql
  - MongoDB
- 8. REDIS
- 9. Unit Testing
- 10. Git, Github
- 11. Linux Server
- 12. NGINX

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Job 2012 – present

# Web Based System Developer

Jakarta

#### Responsibilities:

- Writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices
- Creating website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS/Java Script/Frame Works practices
- Make recommendations on the use of new and emerging technologies
- Integrating data from various back-end services and databases
- Building customized web based system to the highest specifications.
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs
- Create and maintain software documentation
- Be responsible for maintaining, expanding, and scaling our site.

#### **Construction Field Coordinator**

August 2015 - March 2017

# **PT. Surya Kusuma** ~ *Building and Engineering Contractor* Jakarta

#### Responsibilities:

- Discussing requirements with the potential clients
- Kick of Meeting with potential clients
- Assessing the environmental impact and risks connected to projects

- Judging whether projects are workable by assessing materials, costs and time requirements
- Drawing up blueprints, using Computer Aided Design (CAD) packages
- Provide the Bill of Quantity (BOQ)
- Preparing bids for tenders, and reporting to clients, public agencies and planning bodies
- Undertaking technical and feasibility studies including site investigations (e.g soil durability, drainage, electricity, etc.)
- Liaising with clients and a variety of professionals including architects and subcontractors
- Making sure sites meet legal guidelines, and health and safety requirements.
- Managing, directing and monitoring progress during each phase of a project
- Plan ahead to prevent problems and resolve any emerging ones
- Coordinate and direct construction workers and subcontractors
- Review the work progress on daily basis
- Ensure quality construction standards and the use of proper construction techniques
- Prepare internal and external reports pertaining to job status
- Reconcile check-list according to Bill of Quantity (BOQ) with client
- Hand overing finished product to the client/s

**Facility Coordinator** 

July 2012 – August 2015

**Weatherford Indonesia** - http://www.weatherford.com Bekasi

Responsibilities:

#### **Maintenance & Facility Management Roles:**

- Maintain and monitoring subsidiary office such as Talavera Based, Narogong Based, Balikpapan Based, Duri (Riau) Based
- Maintain office and workshop equipment, physical space and telecommunications systems for a Building or Base.
- Schedule preventative maintenance, respond to urgent maintenance calls and participate in the creation of emergency preparedness plans

#### **Administrative and Management System Roles:**

- Building the Web based Requisition Portal system based on previous share point system
- Developing Web based Requisition Portal system for organized and manageable repair and maintenance request
- Managing and Full filling departments/business units requests or requirements
- Applying for required environmental permits (Hazardous Substances)
- Monitoring tools & equipment certification and calibration
- To monitor and follow up CPAR (Corrective Preventive Action Request) and NCR (Non Conformance Record) status throughout all division and help departments to close out on time.
- Coordinate weekly Operation meeting with Business Units and Business Supports

#### **Weatherford Indonesia** - http://www.weatherford.com Jakarta

#### Responsibilities:

- Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers and scanners
- Planning and undertaking scheduled maintenances and upgrades
- Communicate to clients or computer users to determine the nature of problems
- Responding to breakdowns such as trouble on servers, data and voice.
- Investigating, diagnosing and solving computer software and hardware faults
- Repairing equipment and replacing parts
- Supervising 3 rd party junior engineering and technical staff (IT)
- Agreeing time-scales based on project requirements.
- Obtaining replacement or special components, fixtures or fittings
- Checking computer equipment for electrical safety
- Maintaining records of software licenses
- Managing stocks of equipment, consumables and other supplies

#### **IT Infrastructure**

November 2006 – August 2009

#### PT. Eptco Dian Persada - Assigned for BP Tangguh LNG Project West Papua

#### Responsibilities:

- Managing Hardware, Software inventory and Licenses. Supporting users (Application & Hardware Support).
- System Windows 2003 Server Active Directory Administration.
- Firewall Administration and Monitoring (Cybercam & Cisco ASA).
- IP Phone configuration (Cisco Products).
- Server Installation such as Physical Server or VMware (Blade Server).
- Storage Area Network Administration.
- VLAN Administration, Switching and Routing. Lotus Domino Server and Lotus Notes Client Administration.
- Local Area Network (LAN) and Wide Area Network Monitoring.
- Internet User Administration(Microsoft ISA Server).
- Internet link migration, Upgrade Metro Ethernet bandwith.
- Symantec BackupExec Administration & Monitoring.
- IT Network Drawing and Cost Estimation for new Project plan.

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science, Informatics University of Computing (UNIKOM) - Bandung, West Java – Indonesia 2014

## **TRAINING**

•	CCNA Intensive - Interconnecting Cisco Network Device - ICND v4.0, Bandung	2010
•	ITIL - IT Infrastructure Library v. 3.0, Jakarta	
•	Weatherford APAC Certified ComCAM Torque Bucking Unit Operator and	2010
	Calibrator, Kemaman – Malaysia	2013
•	Fire Fighting, Internal Weatherford – Jakarta	
•	First Aider, Internal Weatherford – Jakarta	2014
•	Fundamental if Rigging, The Crosby Group - Jakarta	2014
•	Heavy Rigging Application, The Crosby Group - Jakarta	2014
-	ricary rigging Application, The Globby Gloup - barkarta	2014

## **PERSONAL INTERESTS**

- Music
- Photography
- CAD Design
- Web Apps Development using PHP, MySql, Javascript and other various frameworks